Han Dai

hayetdai129@gmail.com

QUALIFICATIONS SUMMARY

I am a senior student study at University of Limerick right now. At the same time, I am the contributing editor for Crossing, a global opinion sharing platform based in Taiwan, which trained me as a person who can work under strict deadline and conquer the time differences. I assist in managing their social media, create the content, and develop the new topics for the readers.

After working in three different magazines, I honed the skill to catch the trend and also some SEO knowledge. Those experiences trigger my interest in learning Web development and audience research, so I take the sociology of media audience class in UL this semester and self-learning web development in my free time.

WORK EXPERIENCE & ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Bali International Film Festival: Bali, Indonesia

The longest running annual International Film Festival in Indonesia

Marketing Intern | July - August, 2018

Assist in doing the marketing job by researching and translating information from Mandarin sponsors and directors.

- Contact potential sponsors
- E-communicate with filmmakers, influencers, and sponsors

Crossing: Taipei, Taiwan

Global opinion sharing platform gathered over 200 writers from 110 cities around the world

Contributing Editor | November, 2017 - present

Manage Crossing Arab World fan page, provide the global opinion to Mandarin-speaking readers, assist in improving the communication through different cultures, interview and invite professions to join.

- Copywriting to promote the articles
- Online curation: #Book Swap, #Chinese New Year
- Compose Articles: 17Arabic Interview, #Monthly Arab News, #Voice of Middle East, ect.
- Infographics: Iraq Election, Syria's New War Millionaires
- Videos: A Midsummer Night's Dream in Palestine, Message in a Bottle

Cosmopolitan: Taipei, Taiwan

An international fashion magazine for women

Intern Editor | December, 2017 - August, 2018

Delivered the latest fashion, entertainment news and communicate with PR people about interviewing stars or influencers for the magazine. Also, assist the studio shooting and products borrowing from several brands.

- Target the preference of the readers and explore the topic which would attract the attention of the readers
- Follow up the events like Oscar, Met Gala, Special Screening, Royal wedding, Grammy and Party holds by the brand.
- Create the promotion posts for several brands like Charles & Keith, Off-White, Michael Kors, Wave Shine, S'AIME, PUMA, etc.
- Assist in holding B2C events: COSMO summer pool party
- Cooperate with the stylist and help with products borrowing for studio shooting
- Website SEO improvement and SEO writing

Manager Today: Taipei, Taiwan

The best management magazine in Mandarin-speaking area

Intern Editor | February - July,2017

Compose the first-hand management news and entrepreneurship stories for Mandarin-speaking readers. Additionally, use GA to track the performance of articles weekly and make EDM for the readers.

- Research business models and marketing strategies from successful companies
- Compose articles and share business knowledge with the readers
- Track the performance of online material and re-advertise the article to the subscribed readers by EDM

ACADEMIC CREDENTIALS

OTHER

- 17Arabic SEO improvement (2018)
- Google start-up weekend: 360 degrees live App, the first prize (2017)
- NCCU college freshman volleyball game: the first prize (2016)
- Workawayer in Europe (2017 summer), South Asia (2018 summer)
- Next-Step of Fintech study group (2015-2016)
- STP Case Study Group: McDonald Taiwan, SAPPE Thailand, Triumph Global, Dr. Wu Taiwan (2016-2017)
- ATCC Case Competition: Second Round, Team IBM (2017)

Few works for your reference:

- Web Development Works → https://hayets.github.io/personal-project/
- Monthly Arab Music Introduction with Picture → https://reurl.cc/o9kXv
- Humans of Syria Weekly Translation → https://reurl.cc/qm76n
- Agriculture of Cambodia 從銀行踏入田裡──柬埔寨「鮭魚族」返鄉‧立志用科技讓農民擺脫貧窮 → https://bit.ly/2zndy09
- Learning Arabic while helping refugees and women 給台灣人的「阿拉伯語線上教學網站」:17Arabic 要讓約旦「難民」與「女性」都能平等就業 → https://bit.ly/2RGXZrB
- The more nervous you are, the more you need to speak! 3 skills that help you to express your opinion 越緊張,越要開□發言!3 個說話技巧,成為表達觀點的高手→ https://bit.ly/2JnFSXn

Thanks again for your consideration. Best regards, Han Dai